Duty. Country. Family.
Father Soldier Son is a documentary, war film directed by Leslye Davis.
First Class Brian Eisch is critically wounded in Afghanistan, it sets him and
his sons on a journey of love, loss, redemption and legacy.
Himself, played by Brian Eisch.
himself, played by Isaac Eisch.
himself, played by Joey Eisch.
Parliamentary Aide, played by Roxanne Gregory.
Father Soldier Son is a 2020 American documentary film directed
and produced by Catrin Einhorn and Leslye Davis.
It follows the family of Brian Eisch, a Sgt.
First Class in the United States Army, and the effects of his deployment
to the War in Afghanistan has on him and his young sons.
The film was released on July 17, 2020, by Netflix.